
var questions = 
      [
        {
          question:"[1]. I visit you every night even if you dont call me! Im lost every day. What Am I?",
          option1:"A. Moon",
          option2:"B. Venus",
          option3:"C. Stars",
          option4:"D. Sun",
          answer: 3
        },
        
        {
          question: "[2]. Some came from the Sun and Moon, Others from Thor and his hammer are hewn, By Odins beard, and Frigg and Tiw, The last is Saturn, from which we grew.What are we?",
          option1:"A. Origin of names  Days of lunar month",
          option2:"B. Origin of names of days of the week",
          option3:"C. Origin of names of the month of the year",
          option4:"D. Origin of the names of hindu calender",
          answer: 2
        },
        {
          question: "[3]. My farther is the moon, my mother is the sea, I die when I reach land. What am I?",
          option1:"A. River",
          option2:"B. Lake",
          option3:"C. Waves",
          option4:"D. Tides",
          answer: 3
        },
        {
          question: "[4]. Large as a mountain, small as a pea, Endlessly swimming in a waterless sea. What am I?",
          option1:"A. Comet",
          option2:"B. Asteroids",
          option3:"C. Moons",
          option4:"D. Satellite",
          answer: 2
        },
        {
          question: "[5]. Empty as space, Scary as a ghost, I appear every night What am I?",
          option1:"A. Darkness",
          option2:"B. Fire",
          option3:"C. Stars",
          option4:"D. Moons",
          answer: 1
        },
        {
          question: "[6]. Which one of Santa's reindeer can you see in outer space?",
          option1:"A. Comet",
          option2:"B. Asteroids",
          option3:"C. Breker",
          option4:"D. Surge",
          answer: 1
        },
        {
          question: "[7]. Why did Mickey Mouse go to Outer Space?",
          option1:"1. He wants to watch moon ",
          option2:"2. He wants to visit to Mars",
          option3:"3. He wanted to fly in space",
          option4:"4. He wanted to visit pluto",
          answer: 4
        },
        {
          question: "[8]. I'm sometimes full, but I never overflow. What Am I?",
          option1:"1. Sky",
          option2:"2. Moon",
          option3:"3. Earth",
          option4:"4. None",
          answer: 2
        },
        {
          question: "[9]. I am the beginning of the end, as well as the end of time and space. I am essential to creation and I surround every place. What am I?",
          option1:"A. The big bang",
          option2:"B. The big rib",
          option3:"C. The space",
          option4:"D. The letter E",
          answer: 4
        },
        {
          question: "[10]. I can kill people, but without me there would be no people. I was born long ago and will someday die. I can cause fire and am a magician with water. I have more brothers than any person. There is very little that can stop me. What I am?",
          option1:"A. A star ",
          option2:"B. A moon",
          option3:"C. A planet",
          option4:"D. A celestial body",
          answer: 4
        },
        
      ];
